Hello, my friends, and welcome to exercise number 17.
And this exercise, we are asked to find the time complexity of this function.
So this function will give us the product of two numbers it took in Peru meter and a and parameter and
b and it's four return the result as some this type of event post the video, I think about this function
and how to get the time complexity.
Please write them down on the paper and try to solve it and comment it in the comments below.
In order to see your progress and its and your motivation to solve these exercise.
So let's begin, I hope you find the best answer and the correct answer.
And some of equal to zero.
We have all of one.
For NTI, equal to zero, we have a loop.
So I told you that we need to start with the initial condition study that stopping condition and the
way of increment it will go through all elements because I +, + + will go from zero to be so from zero
to be okay, it will go through the elements from zero to me and it depends on the on the value of B.
OK.
Sum equal to the new sum, equal to the old sum plus eight.
OK, so this is executing one.
Only one.
OK.
And now it will return this sum return.
The sum is of one.
Oh, from zero to B and all the all the way through all the elements would be a result from going through
from zero to be so it is of B.
This would be a result in one plus of B plus o of one.
OK.
What is the higher solution, what is the higher order of type B, therefore, the time complexity of
this function is of B why we are doing this in order to tell you that not always depend on and like
and and the value of and here we are, depending on B.
So always try to study the initial the stopping and the weight of increment of all of these exercises.
OK.
In the loop, please, when you see a loop, please study the initial the stuff.